Guide to the Tom Law San Francisco Bay Area Punk and Rock Handbill and Poster Collection M1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes and 1 large map folder
  - Folder 3, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    5. Let's Active; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-10 -- Big City; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-11 -- Husker Du; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-17 -- Big Race; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-18; 8.5x17.
    6. The Looters, Conjunto Cespedes; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-19 -- The Fleshtones, Zeitgeist; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-26; 8.5x17.
    7. Flesh for Lulu, The Naked Into; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-17 -- Beat Farmers, Mojo Nixon; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-24; 8.5x17.
    8. Let's Active, The Higsons; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-10 -- Husker Du; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-17; 8.5x17.
    9. Freaky Executives, Shy Hands; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-16 -- Jesus And Mary Chain, The Flaming Lips, True Believers; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-23; 8.5x17.
    10. Plan 9, Soul Asylum; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-07 -- 10,000 Maniacs, Camper Van Beethoven; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-14 -- Gene Loves Jezebel; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-21; 8.5x17.
    11. The Lyres, The Droogs; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-27 -- Plimsouls, Mercy Seat; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-03; 8.5x17.
    12. The Lyres, Yard Trauma; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-28 -- Blue Riddim; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-04; 8.5x17.
    13. Trouble Funk, The Looters; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-18 -- Voice Farm; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-25; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 4, 1983- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Until December; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-01; 8.5x17.
    2. Basic Black. Wear Black Leather, Get In Free! New Wave Rock Dancing With DJ Alan Robinson - Videos/Lasers; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    3. Snakefinger's Vestal Virgins, Tupelo Chain Sex; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-19 -- Kommunity FK, Faith No More; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-26; 8.5x17.
    4. The Looters, Zulu Spear; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-06 -- Faith No More; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-13 -- Meat Puppets; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-20; 8.5x17.
    5. Patsy Cline & The Memphis G Spots; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-03 -- Scraping Foetus Off The Wheel, Negativeland; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-10 -- Robyn Hitchcock; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-17; 8.5x17.
    6. Zasu Pitts Memorial Orchestra, The Mysteries; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-01 -- Chris Isaak; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-08 -- The Vipers (from N.Y.); I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-15; 8.5x17.
    7. Rank and File, The Muskrats; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-11; -- The Looters; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-18 -- Voice Farm, Until December; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-25; 8.5x17.
    8. Blackouts (from Seattle), Rank And File; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-11-19; 8.5x17.
    9. Sex Gang Children, Fountains Of Use [Fountains Of Youths]; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-05 -- Bluebells; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-12 -- Specimen; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-19; 8.5x17.
    10. The Looters, Moja Nya (Urban Reggae From NYC); I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-23 -- The Cult, Bunnydrums; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-30 -- 54-40; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-06; 8.5x17.
    11. King Kurt, Black Athletes; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-25 -- March Violets; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-04 -- Red Lorry Yellow Lorry; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-18; 8.5x17.
    12. The Fall; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03 -- Red Lorry Yellow Lorry, Crawl Away Machine; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-18; 8.5x17.
    13. Blue Riddim Band, Mapenzi; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-04 -- Rank and File, The Muskrats; I -Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-11; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 5, 1985- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. The Replacements, Pontiac Brothers; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-09 -- Freaky Executives; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-16 -- Jesus And Mary Chain, The Flaming Lips; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-23; 8.5x17.
    2. Poison Girls, Beat Rodeo; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-07 -- Meat Puppets, Poison 13; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-14; 8.5x17.
    3. Club Foot Orchestra; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-18; 8.5x17.
    4. The Cat Heads, Blue Movie, The Furies; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-12-31; 8.5x17.
    5. Crawl Away Machine; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; Fri. 16; 8.5x17.
    6. The Invertebrates; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-18; 8.5x17.
    7. The Invertebrates, Ku Ku Ku; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-18; 8.5x17.
    8. Snakefinger; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-27; 8.5x17.
    9. Beyond The Beat Bash!; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-25; 8.5x17.
    10. Love Club; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-11; 8.5x17.
    11. Fleshlab, Poison Gas Research, DD Downer, Science Project, Nel Stewart; Martin/Weber Gallery; 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    12. Floating Lotus, Sachiko's Culture Shock!; La Pena; 3105 Shattuck Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-03-28; 8.5x17.
    13. Moit Moit, Boomer, Nonfiction; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-06; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 6, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Unrest In The Nest; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; May 7 & 8; 8.5x17.
    2. [Amharic]; Lion's Night. Live Reggae & Ethiopian Music. I-Tal. Vi-tal. Guiness. Videos. Sound System; 3134 Grove St. Berkeley, CA; September 1; 8.5x17.
    3. Yanks; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-21; 8.5x17.
    4. Turn Me Loose Night. DJ Dancing Followed By "Small Cognito." With San Francisco's Most Esoteric Dee Jay Terry Mercenary; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    5. Richard Montoya, Slick Ric, Goosey Guzman, M.E. Estrella, Xipetotec, Spain Rodriguez, Rene Yanez, Richard Talavera, Carl Heyward, Dominique; Club Nine; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-19; 8.5x17.
    6. Shiva Dancing; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-11; 8.5x17.
    7. Ha Ha; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-17; 8.5x17.
    8. American Music Club [AMC], The Wankers; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-11; 8.5x17.
    9. American Music Club [AMC], Housecoat Project; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-07; 8.5x17.
    10. Snakefinger; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-04; 8.5x17.
    11. Say The Word, The Vipers; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-26 -- Say The Word; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-19; 8.5x17.
    12. The Naked Into; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-31 -- The Naked Into, American Music Club; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-01; 8.5x17.
    13. The Naked Into; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-03; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 7, 1985- 1987 (Box 3)
    1. Nanos Valaoritis, Tribal Warning Theatre, Terra Incognita, Resolutely Bloom, Peter Plate, Jim Martin, Cyrnai; Gumption Theater; 1563 Page St. San Francisco, CA; February 14; 8.5x17.
    2. It's A KUSF Simulcast [sign used in club?]; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    3. Bardo [Bardo Productions], Ped Xing; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-11; 8.5x17.
    4. The Fibonaccis; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-30; 8.5x17.
    5. Spot 1019, The Whitefronts; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-09; 8.5x17.
    6. Pray For Rain (Formerly The Big Race), The Naked Into; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-28; 8.5x17.
    7. Poser The [Plain]Clothesman; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-18; 8.5x17.
    8. Boss Hoss, Slovenly; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-13; 8.5x17.
    9. Shocking U; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-07; 8.5x17.
    10. Flying Color, The Cat Heads, Blue Movie, The Furies, Terra Incognita; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-12-31; 8.5x17.
    11. [calendar]; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1987-03 [?]; 8.5x17.
    12. New York's East Village Art Scene Video Tape, David Howard; Vorpal Gallery; 444 Market St.? 393 Grove St.? San Francisco, CA; 1985; 8.5x17.
    13. Frightwig, Jungle Studs, Any Three Initials [A3I]; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-09; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 8, 1984- 1996 (Box 3)
    1. Us Girls; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-10; 8.5x17.
    2. [many]; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-19; 8.5x17.
    3. Black Athletes, King Kurt; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-25; 8.5x17.
    4. Trial; New Langton Arts; 1246 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; July 20; 8.5x17.
    5. Jungle Dinner; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; February 19 -- Jungle Dinner; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; February 3 -- Jungle Dinner; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; February 17; 8.5x17.
    6. The Invertebrates, Gleaming Spires, Mechanical Bride; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 8.5x17.
    7. Next To Nothing [Next To Nothin'], Uh-Oh; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1996-01-01; 8.5x17.
    8. The Vandals, The Afflicted, The Hot Spit Dancers; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-22; 8.5x17.
    9. Nip Drivers; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-16; 8.5x17.
    10. Agent Orange, Soldiers Of Fortune, Black Athletes; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-03-26; 8.5x17.
    11. Modmach, Popart (L.A.); V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-06; 8.5x17.
    12. Dive In; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-28; 8.5x17.
    13. Zulu Spear, Too Much Fun; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-08; 8.5x17.
    14. The Cuban Next Door, Marz Band; Heaven's Gate; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; October 26; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 9, 1982- 1985 (Box 3)
    1. Glorious Din, Paranoid Blue; YMCA; 220 Golden Gate San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-09; 8.5x17.
    2. Candace Natvig & Jon English; 2019 Blake St. Berkeley, CA; 1982-09-19; 8.5x17.
    3. Dexter Devoe, Rick Mills; 2140 Club; 2140 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-17; 8.5x17.
    4. Frightwig, Glorious Din, M.J.B., Shiva Dancing, Camper Van Beethoven; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-01; 8.5x17.
    5. Too Much Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-31; 8.5x17.
    6. This Is Spinal Tap, A Hard Days Night; Roxie Theatre; 3117 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984; 8.5x17.
    7. Zula Pool; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12; 8.5x17.
    8. Zulu Spear, Too Much Fun; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-21; 8.5x17.
    9. Zef, Mr. White, Guitar; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; July 24; 8.5x17.
    10. Zef, Mr. White, Guitar; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; July 24; 8.5x17.
    11. Voluntary Living; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-07; 8.5x17.
    12. Voluntary Living; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-02; 8.5x17.
    13. X-Tal; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-07; 8.5x17.
    14. White Stagg Band; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-21; 8.5x17.
    15. Vision; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-19; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 10, 1985- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Impulse F, Z Axis; Bay Brick Inn; 1190 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-06; 8.5x17.
    2. Wages Of Sin, Shiva Dancing, Silent Night; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-25; 8.5x17.
    3. Eyes Of God; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-06; 8.5x17.
    4. Modmach; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-22; 8.5x17.
    5. Too Much Fun; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07; 8.5x17.
    6. Too Much Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-17; 8.5x17.
    7. The Toasters; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-19; 8.5x17.
    8. Three Day Stubble, Housecoat Project; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-30; 8.5x17.
    9. Death Ranch, Modmach; Bannam Place; 50a Bannam Alley San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-24; 8.5x17.
    10. Terra Incognita, Peter Plate, Brain Rust, Cyrnai, Tribal Warning Theatre, Suzanne Thomas; New College Of California; 777 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-07; 8.5x17.
    11. Scott Alexander, Maria McElroy, Chuck Z; Media; 360 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-16; 8.5x17.
    12. Michael Covino, Young Roginsky, Aaron Noble, Harvey Stein; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-24; 8.5x17.
    13. Unruly World; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-30; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 11, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Gil Scott-Heron, Linda Tillery and her band, Dr. Charlie Clements; Berkeley Community Theatre; 1900 Allston Way Berkeley, CA; 1986-02-09; 8.5x17.
    2. Christel Harth, Saxophonist Arturo Smith. Shadows In Light; The Lab; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    3. Next New Years Eve. Dancing 10pm-6am! Party Parade. Thu-Sun 10pm-5am Diagonal Dancing; Next, The [Next Club/Lipps]; 201 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    4. [many], Lockdown; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-08; 8.5x17.
    5. Thessalonians, Psyclones, Breather, Ex-I, Consternation Of Pain, Last Casino In Nirvana, Hinton Templar, TV A.R.M. Video Screenings; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-10; 8.5x17.
    6. Aaron Noble, Peter Plate, Anita Valerio, Plus a Tape From Sabina Ott; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-21; 8.5x17.
    7. Free Burdening; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-21; 8.5x17.
    8. Naked Spaces. Living Is Round; Red Vic Movie House; 1659 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-12; 8.5x17.
    9. The Four Corners, Bardo; Southern Exposure Gallery At Project Artaud; 401 Alabama St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-21; 8.5x17.
    10. Pamala Stanley, Paul Parker, Yourselves; Galleria Design Center; 101 Kansas St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-18; 8.5x17.
    11. Maxiwhack, Live On Stage; Nob Hill Cinema; 729 Bush St. San Francisco, CA; 1985; 8.5x17.
    12. The Haters, Human Head Transplant, Installation/Miles Standish; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; April 12; 8.5x17.
    13. Mimzabim; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-28; 8.5x17.
    14. Songbirds Of Central Nevada; Bill Talen Intersection; 756 Union St. San Francisco, CA; August 18-21, 25-28; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 12, 1981- 1985 (Box 3)
    1. The Black Magic Rydim Rockers, Guest Comedian; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-20; 8.5x17.
    2. Pierre Early Sings With The Change Band; Major Pond's; 2801 California St. San Francisco, CA; 1981-04-04; 8.5x17.
    3. Sleepwalk. Photographic Installation Tracy Mostovoy with Text By Anita Valerio. Two Evenings Of Eroto-Comatose Lucidity. "Debt Begins at 20", Film Of The Pittsburgh Punk Scene of '78. Stephanie Beroes. [etc.] "The Parking Lot/The Criminal" A Dialogue/Distortion By Anita Valerio With Luna Discussion And Tim O'Neill. "Slumber Of The Christ Child" Anita Valerio With Frank Discussion; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09; 8.5x17.
    4. Elbows Akimbo; The Lab; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; April 17-18; 8.5x17.
    5. The Invertebrates, Gleaming Spires, Mechanical Bride; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 8.5x17.
    6. The Invertebrates, Terra Incognita, Pamela Z; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-22; 8.5x17.
    7. The Invertebrates, Terra Incognita; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06; 8.5x17.
    8. Teknofear; Major Pond's; 2801 California St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-11 -- Teknofear; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-31 -- Teknofear; Club Nine; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-10 -- Teknofear; Zulu Party; San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-14; 8.5x17.
    9. Impulse F, Fountains Of Use; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-12; 8.5x17.
    10. Great Guns; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; May 10; 8.5x17.
    11. Ha Ha; Last Day Saloon; 406 Clement St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-17; 8.5x17.
    12. Impulse F; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-29; 8.5x17.
    13. Impulse F, Crawl Away Machine; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-22; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 13, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Rebuild Crossroads, Berkeley. Zulu Warriors. 24 Teach-In/Cultural Event Against Apartheid. Bring Your Shanty; University of California, Berkeley. Biko/Sproul Plaza; Berkeley, CA; 1986-04-29; 8.5x17.
    2. Club Foot Orchestra; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-09; 8.5x17.
    3. Glorious Din, M.J.B. [Mint Julep Ballet], Beat Happening, Brain Rust, X-Tal; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-22; 8.5x17.
    4. Snappers; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-07 -- Snappers; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-28; 8.5x17.
    5. Black Dolls, Fire Mission, Diet Tribe; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-05; 8.5x17.
    6. Esmerelda, Slantstep, Secret Sons Of The Pope; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-04; 8.5x17.
    7. Esmerelda, Slantstep, Secret Sons Of The Pope; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-04; 8.5x17.
    8. Bomber; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-04; 8.5x17.
    9. The Refugees; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-11; 8.5x17.
    10. Vision; El Rio; 3158 Mission St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-16; 8.5x17.
    11. Wages Of Sin, Elliot Schneider, Ku Ku Ku; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15 -- Wages Of Sin, Lethal Gospel, Last Rites; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-10; 8.5x17.
    12. Blue Movie; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-29; 8.5x17.
    13. Freaky Executives, Cindy, DNZ; Oakland Hyatt Regency Ballroom; Oakland, CA; 1985-11-24; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 14, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Wheeler Cole, Andrew Potter, Rich Kesler, Ned Van Alstyne; Valencia Rose; 766 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; Nov. 27-28; 8.5x17.
    2. [many]; [many]; San Francisco; Richmond; Oakland, CA; 8.5x17 -- Imelda; Club Nine; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; April 8-19; 8.5x17.
    3. Lethal Gospel, Mess Tent, Hard Ones; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-02; 8.5x17.
    4. Renegades Of Funk. Featuring Members Of The Looters, Big City, Mapenzi. And CK Ladzepko, Rocki Dzidzornu + Victor Tieku; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-22; 8.5x17.
    5. Denim TV; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-11; 8.5x17.
    6. Comedy Troupe Culture Clash; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-16; 8.5x17.
    7. Zulu Spear; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-29; 8.5x17.
    8. Shy Hands; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-18; 8.5x17.
    9. Fade To Black, Our Lady Of Pain, TBA; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-31 -- Black Athletes; Redd Kross; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-07 -- Redd Kross; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-22 -- Agent Orange; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-29; 8.5x17.
    10. Shy Hands; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-02 -- Shy Hands; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-01; 8.5x17.
    11. Too Much Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-12; 8.5x17.
    12. Zulu Spear; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; September 14; 8.5x17.
    13. Terra Incognita; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-31; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 15, 1983- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Funhouse, P. Zuzu & K. Komo [P.K.], Thieves' Cross; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-18 -- Funhouse, Thieves' Cross; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; August 19; 8.5x17.
    2. The Invertebrates, Arms Of Venus, American Music Club; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-07-16; 8.5x17.
    3. Jeffrey Normal & Magick; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; November 27; 8.5x17.
    4. Jain, Z Axis; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-22; 8.5x17.
    5. A Is A; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; August 28; 8.5x17.
    6. Altar De Fey, Specimen; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-19 -- Altar De Fey; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-18 -- Altar De Fey; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-24; 8.5x17.
    7. O.J. Ekemode and the Nigerian Allstars, Zulu Warriors; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-28; 8.5x17.
    8. The Defectors (Featuring Former Members Of Nuns/Rude Girl, Jain and Da-Da), Wages Of Sin, Special Guest appearance By Kathleen McGuire Of Big City; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-08; 8.5x17.
    9. The Defectors, Fallen Angel, DJ Bernard, Live Nude Boys; Electricity City; 452 Shotwell St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-12; 8.5x17.
    10. Chief Commander Ebenezer Obey And The Inter-Reformers Band; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15; 8.5x17.
    11. Temper Temper; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-14; 8.5x17.
    12. Legal Reins; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-09 -- Legal Reins, Mrs. Green, The Cat Heads; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-10; 8.5x17.
    13. Nothing Sacred; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
    14. Crawl Away Machine, Time Beach; Baybrick Inn; 1190 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-30; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 16, 1983- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Crawl Away Machine; Swedish American Hall; 2174 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-07; 8.5x17.
    2. Monks Of Perpetual Indulgence; Harvey Milk Plaza; Market St. & Castro San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-23; 8.5x17.
    3. Junglebook, Pamela Z, Mark Pritchard; Noe Valley Ministry; 1021 Sanchez St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-28 -- Junglebook, Dega Ray, Pamela Z, Spider Box; Spider Box; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-27; 8.5x17.